

CONTACT

- +880181627303
- Apon Bhabon (7th Floor),
 Golden City, Safipur Bazar,
 Kaliakoir, Gazipur

SKILLS

MS Power BI

- ETL Data Modeling
- DAX Measures Data Visualization

MS Excel

- Data Cleaning Pivot Tables
- Power Pivot Function & Formula
- Graphs & Charts

SQL

COURSES & TRAINING

"Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate" by Coursera

"Data Analytics Boot Camp" by Sabbir

LANGUAGES

English - Speaking, Writing & Reading Bangla – Mother Tonge

MOHAMMAD HASAN MIA

Assistant Accounts Manager

Analytical, detailed oriented accountant with a history of accurately and effectively supporting accounting activities. 8+ years of experience in presenting data, analyzing cost, providing financial reports under time pressure. Dedicated to provide exemplary work & supporting the overall mission of the department and company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

C. P. Bangladesh. Co., Ltd

Jan 2015 - Present

Section Manager – Accounts & Finance

Nov 2023 - Present

Major Responsibilities:

- Assist in preparation of monthly & yearly financial statements.
- Calculate the cost of product & cost of goods sold
- Analyze & monitor the cost associated with the company's product.
- Conduct month end account closing activities.

Senior Officer – Accounts & Finance

Jan 2018 - Oct 2023

Major Responsibilities:

- Calculate the cost of product & cost of goods sold for each product.
- Check daily expenditure, vouchers, bills & requisition slips.
- Prepare payment voucher, journal voucher, receipt voucher etc.
- Deduct appropriate Tax & VAT from vendors'/suppliers' invoices.

Officer - Accounts & Finance

Jan 2015 - Dec 2017

Major Responsibilities:

- Handling all cash & bank related activities.
- Prepare bank reconciliation statement.
- Daily recording & posting of transactions in the ERP software.
- Arrange suppliers' payment through cheque, RTGS/BEFTN.

EDUCATION

Master of Business Administration (MBA)

Accounting & Information Systems Jagannath University, Dhaka

CGPA: 3.29 (Out of 4)

2014

Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA)

Accounting & Information Systems

Jagannath University, Dhaka

CGPA: 3.34 (Out of 4) 2013

REFERENCES

Mr. Abdullah Al Mamun

General Manager C. P. Bangladesh Co., Ltd.

Mob: 01766-668853

Mr. Anup Kumar Sarkar

Department Manager
C. P. Bangladesh Co., Ltd.

Mob: 01730-325273